A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9 FA379
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller vice presidential records, National Commission on Water Quality, Series 9
1973-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
United States. Office of the Vice President
Mitchell, Donna R.
FA379
72.5 record cartons 55 record storage boxes, one 17x11 oversize box
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
President Gerald R. Ford nominated Nelson A. Rockefeller to fill the vacant vice presidency following the resignation of President Richard M. Nixon in August 1974. Rockefeller served as Vice President from December 19, 1974, to January 20, 1977.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 26 9
Arrangement note
Folders are rarely in chronological or alphabetical order. For example, the first boxes deal with the closing of the commission. Most boxes seem to be organized according to topic.
Scope and Contents note
NOTE TO RESEARCHERS
This series contains the office files of Donna R. Mitchell, a member of Nelson A. Rockefeller's staff. These files document official activities in the execution of her duties as a member of Rockefeller's staff. Unless a document is specifically addressed to or from Nelson A. Rockefeller, or is referred to in a document addressed to him, it should not be assumed he saw the document or was aware of its existence or substance. Furthermore, researchers should bear in mind that staff files may contain documents or drafts addressed to Rockefeller that were never shown to him.
SCOPE AND CONTENT
The National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ) was formed in1972 by President Richard Nixon, who appointed Nelson A. Rockefeller (then-governor of New York) chair of the Commission. It was an outgrowth of the 1972 Water Pollution Control Act. The Commission got off to a late start: The first meeting was in May 1973. It did not meet its reporting deadline of October 1975 but continued into 1976. The Commission consisted of five members from the public sector and ten from Congress--five each from both chambers. Senator Edmund Muskie and Senator Robert Jones co-chaired the Commission. (Throughout the collection, there is evidence of in-fighting between Rockefeller and Muskie.) The staff of 60 was headed by General Frederick Clarke.
The papers in this collection are those of Donna R. Mitchell. Mitchell, who had been Deputy Director of Rockefeller's Washington office while he was governor of New York, was appointed assistant to the chairman of the NCWQ. She was the key point person between the commission and the staff. She was also Rockefeller's confidential source of information about all aspects of the project as indicated in various memos. (Boxes 21, 22, and 23 contain Mitchell's own reports on New York State Federal Legislation to the Executive Chamber and Albany State Agencies from 1959 to 1967.)
Most significantly, this series consists of hundreds of studies done under contract with outside organizations. The commission spent $11.6 million of its $15 million budget on contracts. The reports cover five broad areas: Technology and Cost Studies (Boxes 31-37); Economic, Social, and Benefit Studies (Boxes 38-42); Environmental Studies (Boxes 42-46); Institutional Studies (Boxes 46-48); and Regional Studies (Boxes 48-53). The material incorporates legal studies of the all-important Public Law 92-500 (the 1972 Amendments to the Federal Water Pollution Control Act). As well, the series contains hundreds of newspaper and magazine clippings covering pollution, industry, treatment centers, water quality, and the politics of the NCWQ.
Additionally, these papers contain Nelson Rockefeller's correspondence with governors, cities, industries, and environmentalists. Boxes 26 and 27 contain Rockefeller's chronological correspondence from 1973 to 1976.
The series also documents the development of the staff's substantial report to the commission (Boxes 14-16, with the final copy in Box 55). The report went through three drafts and then underwent hearings in five major U.S. cities, with Rockefeller presiding over the hearings in Washington, DC (Boxes 17-18). A surprising lacuna of the collection is documentation of the drafting and discussion of the Commission's final report to Congress, which does not appear.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Richard Allison (FA377)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Central Files (FA378)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, New York Office (FA380)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Joseph E. Persico (FA381)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Press Releases (FA382)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Speeches (FA383)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Working Papers of the Vice President (FA384)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Vice Presidential Records, Foreign Affairs and National Security (FA385)
International relations; Technology; United States; Veterans -- United States; Federal government -- United States; Government policy; Human rights; International economic relations; Education -- United States; Energy; Environmental policy; Environmental sciences; Drug control; Economic policy; Economics; Education; Water conservation; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Water -- Purification; Water -- Pollution; International relations -- United States; National security -- United States; Political science; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Presidents -- United States -- Election -- 1976; Prevention and health; Public health; Public policy; Social policy; Social problems; Social sciences
- Commission's Report to Congress, March 18, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Repositories for Commission Reports (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Scope and Contents note
  Enclosed: List of Commission and Contractor Reports
- Study Plans of Commission (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Staff Technical Backup Documents to Staff Report to National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ), April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Technical Volumes - Technology Assessment (1 Volume) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Technical Volumes - Economic and Social Impacts (Volume 1) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Technical Volumes - Economic and Social Impacts (Volume 2) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Technical Volumes - Economic and Social Impacts (Volume 3) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Technical Volumes - Economic and Social Impacts (Volume 4) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Technical Volumes - Environmental Impact Assessment (Volume 1) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Technical Volumes - Environmental Impact Assessment (Volume 2) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Technical Volumes - Regional Impacts (Volume 1) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Note: There was no backup document for the Institutional Assessment chapter of the Staff Report.
- Technical Volumes - Draft Staff Report to Commission, November 1975 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Technical Volumes - Draft Staff Report to Commission - Chapter I - Issues & Findings, November 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Technical Volumes - Staff Report to Commission, April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Technical Volumes - Domestic Council Task Force Report, October 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Technical Volumes - Library of Congress Study Plan, March 1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  With draft study by Lynton, Mields & Coston, February 1973
- Technical Volumes - Public Law 92-500 - "Federal Water Pollution Control Act Amendments of 1972", October 18, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Administration - Correspondence Procedures (Gov. & VP Offices) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  Includes misc. correspondence
- Administration - General Services Administration Agreement for Support Services, w/National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ) (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Administration - Office Space with Floor Plans (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Administration - Secretariat (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Administration - Stationary (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Administration - Travel / Per Diem / Consultant Pay for Commissioners (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Administration - Billings, Leon (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Administration - Billings/Jorling: Definition of BPWTT and Secondary Treatment (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Administration - Braun, Theodore W. (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Administration - Chairman's Authorities (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Administration - Charter for Commission (sec. 15 of PL92-500) Along with "Charge to National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ)" (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Administration - Commission: Executive Committee (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Commission Members - Bios and Photos (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Commission Members - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Commission Members - NAR and Members' Exchange of Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Commission Members - Commission's Name (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Commission Members - Delegation of Authority (from Chairman to Staff) (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Commission Members - Diamond, Henry L. (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Environmentalists - General Items - Exchange of Correspondence with Chairman (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Environmentalists - Conservation Foundation (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Environmentalists - Graphics (Nadia Williams) (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Environmentalists - Muskie, Sen. Edmund S. (Correspondence with NAR) (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Environmentalists - Muskie, Sen. Edmund S. (General) (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Procedures - Consultant and Contractor Selection (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Procedures - Rules of (with Amendments re: Open Meetings) (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Procedures - Open Meetings (Sunshine Act) (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Procedures - Membership: Chairmanships and Organizing the Commission and Study (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Staff - Administrative Officer (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Staff - Assistant to Chairman (Donna R. Mitchell) (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Staff - Availability of Top Staff to Termination of National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ) (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Staff - Conflict of Interest (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Staff - Consultants (Payroll, Contractor and Unpaid) (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Staff - Counsel (Thomas E. Cahill) (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Staff - Delegations of Authority (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Staff - Deputy Program Director (James N. Smith) (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Staff - Executive Director (Frederick J. Clarke) (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Staff - Executive Director and Staff Candidates (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Staff - General (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Staff - Intergovernmental Personnel Act (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Staff - Organization Charts, Rosters and Pay Scales (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Staff - Picnic, at 2500 Foxhall Rd., July 15, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Staff - Program Director (Joe G. Moore, Jr.) (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Staff - Public Relations / Press (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Staff - Staff Assistants to Members (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Staff - NAR Thank-you Letters to Staff, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Staff - Status/Progress Reports (Incomplete) (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Staff - Waugh, Mack C. (Reports on Public Views), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Staff - Billings, Leon (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Staff - NAR Letters to Commission Members, March 1976 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Staff - NAR Letters to Commission Staff, April 1976 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Staff - Termination and Close of Commission Activities (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Staff - Audit by General Accounting Office (GAO) (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Staff - National Archives - Transfer of NCWQ Files, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 71)
- Staff - Rockefeller Archives (NCWQ) (Box 3, Folder 72)
- Staff - Appropriations and Budget for FY '73 and FY '74, 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 73)
- Staff - Appropriations and Budget for FY '75, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 74)
- Staff - Appropriations and Budget for FY '75 (Supplemental), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 75)
- Staff - Appropriations and Budget for FY '76 (Supplemental), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 76)
- Staff - Budget for National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ), 1973-74 (Box 3, Folder 77)
- Staff - Budget for National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ), 1975-76 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  Includes events leading to 1976 "budget crisis"
- Budget - Accounting of February 12, 1967, Updated Through March 13, 1976, 1967-1976 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  Prepared for "budget crisis"
- Budget - 1976 (February - April) - "Budget Crisis" (Box 3, Folder 80)
- Budget - Availability of the "866" Money (FY '74 Appropriation), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 81)
- Budget - Accounting ($17 Million Expenditure), May 1 - July 31, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 82)
- Budget - Budget Breakdown for Study Plan (Box 3, Folder 83)
- National Academy of Sciences - September 1, 1972 Committee Meeting and May '73 report to Public Works Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 84)
- National Academy of Sciences - Commission on Water Quality Policy (Establishment & Membership), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 85)
- National Academy of Sciences - Activities of 1974 and 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 86)
- National Academy of Sciences - Dr. Reds Wolman's Comments, July - September 1975 (Box 3, Folder 87)
- National Academy of Sciences - Review of Industry Contractor Reports, January 1975 (Box 3, Folder 88)
- National Academy of Sciences - Contract with EPA (July 8, 1974) and NAS Marine Studies (Box 3, Folder 89)
- National Academy of Sciences - January 22, 1974 and February 21, 1974 Reports on Technology Capability and Costs (Box 3, Folder 90)
- National Academy of Sciences - February 21, 1974 Report to NCWQ (Study Plan, Suggestions) (Box 3, Folder 91)
- National Academy of Sciences - Reports on Water Use and Secondary Treatment, February 1975 (Box 3, Folder 92)
- National Academy of Sciences / Institute for Ecology - Joint Panel on Ecosystems Analysis, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 93)
- National Academy of Sciences - January 5, 1976 Report on Staff Draft Report of November 1975, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 94)
- National Academy of Sciences - Report on National Residuals Discharge Inventory, January 1976; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 95)
- National Academy of Sciences - Report on National Residuals Discharge Inventory, January 1976; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 3, Folder 96)
- National Academy of Sciences - Review of Final Staff Draft Report, November 1976 (Box 3, Folder 97)
- Study Plan - Library of Congress (Linton, Mields & Costen for Senate Public Works Committee) (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Study Plan - June 7, 1973 by NAR (Box 4, Folder 99)
- Study Plan - Ross Perot - Plan of Action, July 1973 (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Study Plan - Linton, Mields & Coston, June - August, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 101)
- Study Plan - National Academy of Sciences, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  Comments, October 24, 1973 draft; suggestions, February 21, 1974
- Study Plan - Drafts, October 1973 - January 1974 (Box 4, Folder 103)
- Study Plan - Study Program (Proposed) - H. Cook Paper of August 1973 (Box 4, Folder 104)
- Study Plan - Final, January 24, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 105)
- Study Plan - Thoughts About the "Environmental Problem" (Box 4, Folder 106)
- Ross Perot - Background of Controversy (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Ross Perot - Critique of Study Under Contract WQ3AC001 (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Ross Perot - Perot, Ross (EDS) (Box 4, Folder 109)
  Background of reconnaissance study by EDS
- Study Design - Design for Execution of Study Plan; Budget for Each Study Area (Box 4, Folder 110)
- Study Design - Drafts for Implementation as of May 14, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Study Design - Commerce Business Daily (Box 4, Folder 112)
- Study Design - Non-point Sources of Pollution (Agriculture, Urban Runoff, etc.) (Box 4, Folder 113)
- Study Design - Definitions (Box 4, Folder 114)
- Study Design - Integrity (Definition) (Box 4, Folder 115)
- Study Design - Environment and Energy Crisis (Box 4, Folder 116)
- Study Design - Toxics (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Study Design - Groundwater (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Study Design - Selection of Contractors (Box 4, Folder 119)
- Study Design - Work on Municipal Treatment; Economics Industry; Municipal Needs - State's Responses, mid-1974 (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Study Design - Deadlines: Goals and Requirements in PL 92-500 (Box 4, Folder 121)
- Study Design - Water Quality: Effects of Pollution Control, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  H. Cook paper of October 6, 1975
- Effluent Charges - National Commission on Water Quality (NCWQ) Study (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Effluent Charges - Papers by Otto Davis, Allen Kneese, Gardner Brown and Susan Rose-Ackerman (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Effluent Charges - Selected Papers on Subject (Box 4, Folder 125)
- Effluent Charges - Committee for Economic Development Report, April 1974 (Box 4, Folder 126)
- Institutional - Staff (Box 4, Folder 127)
- Institutional - Study Design by Elizabeth Haskell (Box 4, Folder 128)
- Institutional - Study Plan (Box 4, Folder 129)
- Institutional - Study Plan (Box 4, Folder 130)
  8 state samples for study
- Institutional - Study Plan (Box 4, Folder 131)
  Meeting with Dr. Hurt and Dick Dunham in Albany (August 9, 1974)
- Institutional - Study Plan (Box 4, Folder 132)
  Governors' and States' responses to NAR letter of October 24, 1974
- Institutional - Contraction Selection (Box 4, Folder 133)
- Institutional - Public Interest Groups (Conservation Foundation) (Box 4, Folder 134)
- Institutional - Study - Attitudes of Participants (Contract - Oregon Research) (Box 4, Folder 135)
- Institutional - Study - Attitudes (Public Opinion Polls) (Box 4, Folder 136)
- Institutional - Study - Compliance Monitoring (Contract with Energy Resources Co.) (Box 5, Folder 137)
- Institutional - Study - Construction Grants (Contract with Touche Ross) (Box 5, Folder 138)
- Institutional - Study - Problems of "Doers" - (Contracts with Hartley and Price) (Box 5, Folder 139)
- Institutional - Study - Effluent Limitations (Box 5, Folder 140)
- Institutional - Study - Enforcement (Contract with Environmental Law Institute) (Box 5, Folder 141)
- Institutional - Study - Interstate River Basin Authorities (Box 5, Folder 142)
- Institutional - Study - Legal (Statutory Authority) (Box 5, Folder 143)
  Court cases; water rights
- Institutional - Study - Manpower (Box 5, Folder 144)
- Institutional - Study - Permit System (Study Design; Scope of Work; Contractor Selection) (Contract with Energy and Environmental Analysis, Inc.) (Box 5, Folder 145)
- Institutional - Study - Permit System (Blaser & Zeni Proposal) (Box 5, Folder 146)
- Institutional - Study - Planning - Growth Policy (Sewer Line Restrictions and Moratoriums) (Box 5, Folder 147)
- Institutional - Study - Planning (Contract with Harold Wise & Associates) (Box 5, Folder 148)
- Institutional - Study - Public Participation (Contract w/James Ragan & Associates) (Box 5, Folder 149)
- Technology - Staff (Box 5, Folder 150)
- Technology - Scope of Work (Box 5, Folder 151)
- Technology - Contractor Selection (Box 5, Folder 152)
- Technology - Municipal Treatment (Contract with Metcalf & Eddy) (Box 5, Folder 153)
- Technology - Municipal Needs Survey (Contracts with Amer. Pub. Works Assoc. and AMSA) (Box 5, Folder 154)
- Technology - Municipal - Urban (Storm Water) Runoff - Contract with Black, Crow & Eidness (Box 5, Folder 155)
- Technology - Agriculture - Irrigated - (Contract with Toups Corp.) (Box 5, Folder 156)
- Technology - Feedlots (Contract with Development, Planning & Research Assoc.) (Box 5, Folder 157)
- Technology - Nuclear Fusion Torch (Box 5, Folder 158)
- Technology - Land Treatment (Box 5, Folder 159)
- Technology - Innovative (Elimination of Discharge) (Contract with Water Purification Assoc.) (Box 5, Folder 160)
- Technology - Non-Point Sources (Contract with Midwest Research) (Box 5, Folder 161)
- Technology - Industry (Nine Major Water Users) (Box 5, Folder 162)
- Technology - Industry (In-Depth Studies) (Box 5, Folder 163)
- Economic - Staff (Box 5, Folder 164)
- Economic - Study Plan (Box 5, Folder 165)
- Economic - Contractor Selections (Box 5, Folder 166)
- Economic - Economic and Social Studies (Proposal by H. Cook, January 1974) (Box 5, Folder 167)
- Economic - Efficiency in Pollution Control (H. Cook Paper, November 11, 1975) (Box 5, Folder 168)
- Economic - Equity (Discussion Paper- H. Cook, August 15, 1975) (Box 5, Folder 169)
- Economic - Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations (Contract: Agency Agreement WQ4AA001) (Box 5, Folder 170)
- Economic - Brookings Institution (Box 5, Folder 171)
- Economic - Costs Converted to 1975 Figures (Box 5, Folder 172)
- Economic - Interest, Depreciation, etc. (Above Capital Costs) (Box 5, Folder 173)
- Economic - Gross National Product, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 174)
- Economic - Inflation (Box 5, Folder 175)
  Impact of environmental laws and regulations
- Economic - Recession (Box 5, Folder 176)
  Plans to increase spending on water pollution control
- Economic - Supply Constraints (Box 5, Folder 177)
- Economic - Tax-Exempt Pollution Control Bonds (Box 5, Folder 178)
- Economic - Agricultural Industries (Contract with Development Planning & Research Associates) (Box 5, Folder 179)
- Economic - General Industry Study (Contract with National Planning Assoc.) (Box 5, Folder 180)
- Economic - Capital Markets (Contract with Conference Board) (Box 6, Folder 181)
- Economic - Municipal Options (Contract with Meta Systems) (Box 6, Folder 182)
- Economic - Municipal Financing (Contracts with NBER, Data Resources and Meta Systems) (Box 6, Folder 183)
- Economic - Incidence of Costs (Contract with Urban Systems) (Box 6, Folder 184)
- Economic - International Trade (Contract with Public Research Institute) (Box 6, Folder 185)
- Economic - SEAS (Strategic Environmental Assessment System) - CONSAD, IR&T, Control Data, Boeing, et al (Box 6, Folder 186)
- Economic - Social Impacts (Contract with ABT Assoc.) (Box 6, Folder 187)
- NOT USED (Box 6, Folder 188)
- NOT USED (Box 6, Folder 189)
- Economic - Benefits (Beach Closings and Reopenings) (Box 6, Folder 190)
- Economic - Benefits (Commercial Fisheries); Contract with Florida State (Box 6, Folder 191)
- Economic - Benefits (Property Values); Contract with Dornbusch (Box 6, Folder 192)
- Economic - Benefits (Health Aspects of Pollution Control) (Box 6, Folder 193)
- Economic - Staff and Project Directories (Box 6, Folder 194)
- Economic - Study Plan (Box 6, Folder 195)
- Economic - Contractor Selection and Scope of Work (Box 6, Folder 196)
- Economic - Ocean Discharge/Secondary Treatment (Contract with Southern California Coastal Water Research Project) (Box 6, Folder 197)
- Economic - Water Quality Inventory (EPA Report), January 1974 (Box 6, Folder 198)
- Economic - Water Quality Assessment/Evaluation (U.S. Geological Survey) (Box 6, Folder 199)
- Economic - Water Quality Assessment/Evaluation (Paul Eastman proposal, February 7, 1976) (Box 6, Folder 200)
- Economic - Water Quality Assessment/Evaluation (Cook paper on procedure, June 18, 1974) (Box 6, Folder 201)
- Regional - Staff and Project Managers (Box 6, Folder 202)
- Regional - Study Design (Contract with Arthur D. Little) (Box 6, Folder 203)
- Regional - Study Plan (Box 6, Folder 204)
- Regional - Scope of Work for Contracts (Box 6, Folder 205)
- Regional - Contractor Selection (Box 6, Folder 206)
  Related Archival Materials note
  See also, individual river basin folders
- Regional - Chattahoochee - Flint - Apalachicola (Contract with Hammer, Siler, George Assoc.) (Box 6, Folder 207)
- Regional - Colorado River Basin (Contract with Utah State University) (Box 6, Folder 208)